Get more storage space for games and apps by adding external hard drives.
Plug a USB 3.0 drive into your Xbox One. Your Xbox will format the drive
erasing anything that’s on it
and start using it as additional storage space.
The drive has to be at least 256 gigabytes to work.
Plug a second drive in and your Xbox will use that too.
You can use a USB hub to connect both drives to the same port, as long as it’s a USB 3.0 hub.
Two is the maximum at one time,
but you can switch out as many drives as you want.
To move or copy a game or app from one drive to another,
highlight it, press the Menu button on your controller,
and choose Manage game, or Manage app for apps.
Open the drop-down menu and choose move or copy.
Any add-ons you have will also come with it.
A list of storage devices is at the top of your games and apps collection,
so you can always check what’s on each drive.
That’s handy when you want to take your games to a friend’s house.
Bring the drive, plug it into their Xbox One,
and you can play without having to install or download anything.
You do have to be signed into Xbox Live with your own profile.
And if you got the game on disc instead of digital,
you’ll still need to insert the disc to play.
Discover more! Get information and tips from Xbox Help.